ILGWU Motion Picture Films 5780 F
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- "We the People" (Box 375)
  Was container 311. Not on shelf, probably a duplicate entry, 27Aug14/RDM.
- "We've Come of Age" (Box 376)
  Was container 312
- "What's in a Dress" (Box 377)
- "We've Come of Age" (Box 378)
  Was container 312. Not on shelf, probably a duplicate entry, 27Aug14/RDM.
- "What's in a Dress" (Box 379)
- "NY Dressmakers Strike 1958" (Box 380)
  Was container 315
- "Sindicalismo en Accion" (Box 381)
  Was container 316
- "Mother is on Strike" (Box 382)
  Was container 333
- "25th Anniversary of David Dubinsky's Presidency (1957)" (Box 383)
  Was container 334
- "Jinx's Diary: Mobile Health Unit, Tex and Jinx" (Box 384)
  Was container 335 - NOT in cabinet - 4/2015--
- "Dedication of Penn Station South cooperative housing" (Box 385)
  Was container 336
- "Dues and the Union" (Box 386)
  Was container 337
- "Marvin Has It Made" (Box 387)
  Was container 338
- "Unity House" (Box 388)
  Was container 339 -- NOT in cabinet - 4/2015
- "Unity House" (Box 389)
  Was container 340 -- NOT in cabinet 4/2015
- "Triangle Fire Monument" (Box 390)
  Was container 341
- "Mother is on strike" (Box 391)
  Was container 342 -- NOT in cabinet 4/2015 -- Film no.F333:
- "With These Hands" Cornell University (Box 393)
  Was container 344 - Film no.F233:
- "Union Health Center 50th Anniversary Celebration, 1964" (Box 394)
  Was container 345
- "Union Health Center 50th Anniversary Celebration, 1964" (Box 395)
  Was container 346
- Mobile Health Unit on "Tex and Jinx", 1952 (Box 396)
  Was container 347
- "Dedication of Penn South Cooperative Housing, 1962 (Box 397)
  Was container 348
- Film no.F333: "Mother Is On Strike", 1959 (Box 398)
  Was container 349
- Mobile Health Unit; Tex and Jinx bad Kinescope (Box 399)
  formerly box #335